What if I told you one form sufficient to regenerate, you have branded proposal and your GSB
invites, divided into the client and automatically follow, all with a view lifting your finger.
Let me show, see here.
Most freelancers and agencies waste hours, liking proposals, chasing invices, and sending
followers manually, clients sleep through the grass, revenue dates on the table, and here is the
analytics. I fill out this client intake form, name, company, budget, services, and hit
subject. See what happens. Within 60 seconds, see the magic. Yeah, professional, age-related,
Google slide, proposal hits the client inbox, along with matching GSB compliant inbox, and I get
an instant telegram notification, and yeah, see your update. The client clicks, accept or
the client, click here. See here, one click update is here and sends an unloading message to
the client, and add a telegram notification, and they don't respond by clicking either,
accept or decline. The system sends three followers, automated followers, daily, day 7,
day 14, day last bonus ones, fully autopilot bit update on telegram, zero code fully automated,
and built entirely on anything linked in the description.